A Guide to the Records of George Bernard Lorraine, ca. 1925-1976
Library of Virginia
- Real estate records (Box 1-149)
  - Virginia real estate (Box 1-146)
    - Gloucester County (Box 31-42)
      - Beryan Lodge: Herbert Fried, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Berkshire: Hugh Dabney, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Berkshire: John S. Martin, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Berkshire: Dorothy Thompson, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Blythlea: Alfred D. Bell, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Botetourt Hotel: Emily Cocke, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Botetourt Hotel: Augusta Lawson, 1957-1958 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Brentwood: J.B. Hines, 1943-1947 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Briar Patch: Thomas Wheeldon, 1949-1953 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Burks Mill: J.J. Hershaw, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Burleigh: Joe B. Weaver, 1933-1943 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Capahosic Farm: E. Stewart St. James, 1948-1956 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Cary Home: S.W. Kirby, 1946-1955 (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - Cherokee: Cary T. Peebles, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - Claybank: B.L. Rackley, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Clifford: Marianne DeGraff, 1936-1937 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Clifford: John T. Duval, 1953 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Colraine: Jeffrey Parsons, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Colraine: Robert Blake, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Concord Farm: Louis Groh, 1933-1943 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Dragon Ordinary: Kathleen B. May, 1951-1956 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Dunham Massie: H.O. Sanders, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Dunham Massie: 1947 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Dunham Massie: Mrs. Mathew Fontaine Maury Werth, 1968, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Eagle Point: E.C. Rollins, 1937-1949 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Eastover: George Cayle, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Eastover: W.A. Blood, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Elm Bank: W.F. Broaddus, 1930's (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Elmington: Mrs. Stephen C. Wolcott, 1937-1941 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Enfield: R.W. Wilkins, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Exchange: Elinor C. Stewart, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Exchange: Mrs. Darden, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Five Gables: W. Milton Springer, 1945-1947 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Glebe's Bay: Wymond Cabell, 1942-1944 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Glen Roy: Casey Realty Company, 1937, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Greenway on the Severn: Tyler Harris, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Hackberry: G.C. Chewning, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Hael Western: Dennis P. Forrest, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Hermitage: E.B. Somers, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Hockley: L.L. Rice, 1940-1956 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Kaleda: D.B. Kirk, 1955-1968 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Keithock: Runyon Colie, 1941-1942 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Kempville: G.N. Armstrong, 1938-1945 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Kenwood: Walker Buswell, 1947-1951 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Lands End: Wyatt Carneal, 1942-1946 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Lansdowne: Fred Harvie, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Level Green: Charles Marion Fahs, 1937-1938 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Little England: J.E. Critchin, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Little England: 47 acres, 1945 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Little Toddsbury: W.S. Matt, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Marchant Place: J.L. Farinholt, Jr., 1940 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Marlfield: Stanley T. Gray, 1937-1939 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Midlothian: William Moorman, 1934-1950 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Midlothian: William E. Moorman, Jr., 1961 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Minesta: Dave Brown, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Morven: Hugh Dabney, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - New Upton: M.S. Harcum, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Newcomb: Coleman Newcomb, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - Newstand: Margaret A. Tabb, 1933-1937 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Oak Hall: Beulah Davis, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Oak Hall: George R. Brothers, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Old Purton: Thomas P. Duncan, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Pigeon Hill: W.R. Sedgwick, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Pine Harbor: 1 3/4 acres, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Pine Field: John A. Christoffel, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Point Breeze Farm: George Bell, 1940-1956 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Point Lookout: Caroline Sinclair, 1941-1954 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Point Lookout: Isabell Horsley, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Powis on the Ware: C.H. Alexander, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Purton: 1947, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - River Edge Farm: 1970 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Rivermere: Earl Fisher, 1959-1967 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Sandy Knowe: Bank of Gloucester, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Sandy Knowe: S. Quay Koon, 1947-1951 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Seawell's Ordinary: W.C. King, Jr., 1950-1955 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Seven Coves: Darnley Adamson, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Severn Lodge: Wyatt B. Carneal, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Severnby: Katherine P. Withers, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Seward Place: Charles E. Walton, 1937-1955 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Shawan: W.R. Bates, 1942-1956 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Sherwood: Henry A. Williams, 1936-1943 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Shorewood: W.F. Mershon, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Silver Creek: Dr. T.N. Mauck, 1938-1942 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Starrlyn: Rupert Edison Starr, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Summerville: Mary Lee Tabb, 1953-1954 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Thrift Farm: Eddie C. Frazier, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Toddsbury: W.S. Mott, 1933-1950 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Violet Banks: 1936 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Ware Hall: Thomas L. Benson, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Ware Point: C.B. Vaughan, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Ware View: J.B. Weaver, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Warner Hall: J.S. Crockett, 1942-1948 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Warrington: Gloucester Realty Company, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - West End: Oliver B. Whiting, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Whitehall: Harry E.R. Hall, 1935-1938 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - White Hall: John Hayes, 1946-1957 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - White Hall: George R. Squires, 1972-1974 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - White Marsh: C.H. Lawson, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Willow Oak: Clarence G. Stoll, 1962-1964 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Wilson Creek Farm: Leslie de Vergennes-Lavalle, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Wilson Creek Farm: Pat Carter, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Woodside Farm: J.R. Hodges, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Banks, Sidney: 172 acres, 1944 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Barter, Mr: 1.34 acres, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Barton, James: 12 acres, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Bateman, P.A.: 1948-1959 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Birkhofer, Alfred: 39 acres, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Bland, Lola B.: 200 acres, 1936-1942 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Boggs, Frank S.: 40 acres, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Boggs, Frank S.: 66 acres, 1944-1947 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Bonneville, D.E.: 8 acres, 1937-1938 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Bowman, Minnie M.: 1958 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Brimmer, J.T.: 1960 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Bruehl, Anton: 1966 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Brushwood, J.B.: 27 acres, 1943 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Buswell, Walker: 5.88 acres, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Carson, Robb: 79 acres, 1942 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Chapman, Tom: 1952 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - Clay, S.H.: 1949 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Clements, Boyd S.: 1954 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Clements, F.S.: 87 acres, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - Clements, Louis: 1948 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - Cooke, Francis E.: 25 1/2 acres, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - Crittendon, W.W.: 1963 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - Dabney, W.F.: 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Davis, J.G.: 3 acres, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Davison, D.A.: 1945 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Dawson, V.W.: 1955 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Dunham, John M.: 1955 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Dutton, Frank Bland: 1947-1950 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Duval, John T.: 5 acres, 1953-1958 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Euyeart, William R.: n.d. (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Farinholt, Bob: 1940 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Fleming, R.L.: 50 acres, 1933 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Fosque, John: 16 acres, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Glover, Sam: 1942-1947 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Goodwyn, W.G.: 25 acres, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Goodwyn, W.G.: 1957 (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Groh, Louis: 30 acres, 1936 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Guenther, Paul V.: 1944-1945 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Haggerty, E.J.: 1947 (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - Hannevig, Joe B.: 7 acres, 1936-1940 (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - Healy, E.S.: 27 acres, 1947-1948 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Henley, Robert: 3 acres, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - Hogge, A. Henneth: 1948-1954 (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - Hubbard, Gardiner: 16 1/2 acres, 1951 (Box 39, Folder 22)
      - Hutt, J. Clifford: 1960 (Box 39, Folder 23)
      - Jenkins, David M.: 7 acres, 1942 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Jenkins, J.A.: 1944 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Kalaba, Frank M.: 1948-1953 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Kashouty, Ernest: 16.9 acres, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Kemp, B.R.: 18 acres, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Lane, Edward: 7 acres, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Lawson, Hilda: 1954 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - McCue, O.C.: 5.85 acres, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Marten, J.H.: 6 ? acres, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Maury, C.F.: 53 acres, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Miller, E.J.: 18 acres, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Moss, Thomas: 1954 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Nelson, Philip P.: 1960-1962 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Nye, J.H.: n.d. (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - O'Hara, L.R.: 2 acres, 1933, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - Painter, J.L.: 1955 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Palmer, Arthur A.: 89 acres, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Paynter, Mr.: 1 1/2 acres, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Plummer, S.E.: 100 acres, 1937-1946 (Box 40, Folder 19)
      - Register, Parks: 5 acres, 1942-1945 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - Reynolds, H.W.: 1975 (Box 40, Folder 21)
      - Rhode, G.E.: 1957 (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - Riles, E.W.: 1966 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Riley, J.L.: 1953 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - Roberts, R.W., Jr.: 1963 (Box 40, Folder 25)
      - Robius, Thomas P.: 1959 (Box 40, Folder 26)
      - Rowe, Robert F.: 5.8 acres, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 27)
      - Ruthenburg, Louis: 1943 (Box 40, Folder 28)
      - Rutter, Warren: 1959 (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - Sanders, Walter T.: 40 acres, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 30)
      - Scharch, O.W.: 1944 (Box 40, Folder 31)
      - Schwarzschild, Sol: 1950 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Scott, Walker: n.d. (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Seward, Bruce: 1939-1943 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Shepherd, R.T.: 1957 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Sinton, James W., Jr.: 8 acres, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Sinton, James W., Jr.: 1958 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Smith, W.P.: 1947-1948 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Streat, Henry J.: 1947 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Taliaferro, Fannie P.: 40 acres, 1943-1944 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Taliaferro, Earl: 1957 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Taylor, W.R.: 16 acres, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Thomas, Bell: 1952 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Thomas, Paul: 1948 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Tillage, A.H.: 18 acres, 1936-1937 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Turrell, C.R.: 1943 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - Von Schlieben, Hans: 1961 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Walker, R.L.: 1942 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - White, H.R.: 2 acres, 1939 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Williams, James B.: 1947-1952 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Wilson, M.E.: 120 acres, 1930's (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Wolffe, T.B.: 97 1/2 acres, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - Wood, Captain: 1953 (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - Woodland, J.W.: 5 acres, 1944-1949 (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1962 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 42, Folder 2-3)
      - Virginia Historic Buildings Survey real estate listings (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Goochland County (Box 42-45)
      - Aspenwall: Holcombe B. Chamberlain, 1940 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Ben Lomond: 526 acres, 1936 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Ben Lomond: Bill Woodroof, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Bolling Island Farm: Joe Crenshaw, 1942-1962 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Clover Forrest: A. Roy Pearcy, 1942-1945 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Clover Forrest: McKendree G. Fulks, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Deer Lodge: R.J. Jennings, 1940-1945 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Dover: Dr. Blankenbaker, 1947 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Dundonald: Mrs. Cockran, 1945 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Dungeness: Morgan E. Lipps, 1934-1952 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Elk Hill: Buford Scott, 1937-1960 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Elk Hill: Miss Pitts, 1947-1949 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Elk Hill: John Caldwell, 1966-1967 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Elmington: W.H. Moore, 1940-1944 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Fairfield: James H. McDonough, 1942-1959 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Four Oaks: Mr. Wright, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Howard's Neck: J. Boyer Candle, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Island Farm: 1960 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Island Hill Farm: D.H. Boggs, 1933-1959 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Jennings Farm: R.J. Jennings, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Little Dover Farm: D.S. Lewis, 1935, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Longwood: E.H. Harrison, 1935-1938 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - Mannsfield: C.A. Houchins, 1953-1954 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Mount Bernard: Ernest Woodruff, 1935-1942 (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Mount Bernard: Brady Saunders, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Old Elk Hill: Paul H. Dupertuis, 1957-1965 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Orapax Farm: Federal Land Bank, 1938-1940 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Orapax Farm: G.S. Evans, 1952-1955 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Rose Retreat: P.M. Berry, 1935 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Rose Retreat: Tom Pyle, 1948-1956 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Sabot Hill Farm: Bank of Giles County, 1935-1936 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Senito Farm: Maynor Baltimore, 1937-1941 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Snowden: S.B. Stebbins, 1942-1952 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Sunset Hill: Clay Camp, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Tuckahoe: Isabelle Ball Baker, 1936 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Thorncliff: H. Millar, 1942 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Woodlawn: Mr. Taylor, 1934 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Woodville: D.B. Harris, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Barnes, Fred: 30 acres, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Boggs, D.H.: 1945 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Bowles, M.E.: 132 acres, 1940-1941 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Bryan, J. St. George: 1937 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Buchanan, H.B.: 40.45 acres, 1934 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Cal: old church, 1960's (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Clarke, J.L.: 1936 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Gathright: 1933, 1936 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Howell, Arden: 1941 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Hughes, Charles: 1946 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - McLane, W.J.: 14 ? acres, 1936 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - McLane, W.J.: 43 3/4 acres, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Nash, Pope: 1954 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Osbelt: n.d. (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Salter and Williams: farm, 1930's (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - Sloan, June: 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - Trice, Dabney: 150 acres, 1942 (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - Truett, Frances: 110 acres, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - Watkins, Wendell N.: Oilville store, 1935-1940 (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - Wilson, Charles B.: farm, 1941-1955 (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - Woodroof, Bill: 400 acres, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1932-1950, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 22)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Grayson County (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Historic Buildings Survey real estate listings (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Greene County (Box 46, Folder 2-5)
      - C.Q. Dulaney Farm: A.T. Dulaney, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Golden Horse Shoe: R.D. Lyon, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Skyline Drive Cabin: C.P. Kennedy, 1935 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Halifax County (Box 46, Folder 6-13)
      - Bellevue: H.G. Edmunds, 1948-1949 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Berry Hill: Mr. Bruce and Fred E. Watkins, 1945-1950 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Green's Folly: Robert S. Barbour: 1939-1941 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Holmby: W.R. Clark, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Rebel Hill: Ellis Penn, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Tarover: W.B. Caldwell, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Wade, Robert A.: 1944-1945 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Hanover County (Box 46-54A)
      - Ashland Hotel: N.A. Strickland, 1945-1946 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - Axsell Dairy Farm: William Axsel, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 15)
      - Beaver Creek Farm: Fairfax G. Davis, 1942-1943 (Box 46, Folder 16)
      - Beechwood: Alma Carter, 1940-1942 (Box 46, Folder 17)
      - Benvanue: C.C. Cochrane, 1936 (Box 46, Folder 18)
      - Boxley: Helda Van Siller, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 19)
      - Brock Spring: A.C. McKenzies, 1935-1954 (Box 46, Folder 20)
      - Broomfield: Daniel Campbell, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 21)
      - Broomfield: A.A. Farrell, 1958 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Bullfield: Taze Saunders, 1928-1936 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Cabin Hill Farm: John L. Ratcliffe, 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Chantilly: Emma Hope, 1938-1940 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Clazemont: C.G. James, 1937-1941 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Clover Lea: Nancy S.O' Brien, 1933-1953 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Courtland: J.W. Whaley, 1938-1966 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Courtland Farm: G.R. Hudgins, 1936 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Dewberry: Lucile French White, 1934-1943 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Ditchley: J.N. Wright, 1938 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Ditchley: Mrs. Hall, 1961-1964 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Dundonald: Miss Cochran, 1936-1942 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Eagle Point: Walter W. Hayes, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - East View: E.J. Ellsworth, 1936-1940 (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - Eastern View: Charlie L. Turner, 1936 (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - Eastern View: 1961 (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - Edgewood: William C. Noland, 1938 (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - Ellington: Mrs. Vaughan, 1945 (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - Elm Tree Farm: Mr. Barnes, 1939-1952 (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - Elm Tree Farm: W.C. Robinson, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - Fairfield: Mr. Sledd, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - Farmington: 1930's (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Farmington: P.W. Parker, 1945-1948 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Fauber: W.C. Bosher, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Fauber: Jimmie N. Hill, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Fauber: William Lee Mathews, 1967, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Forest: Henri A. Luebbermann, 1945-1952 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Forest: R.J. Ackart, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - French Hay: J.R. Hope, 1939 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - French Hay: Hazel G. Gifford, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Glencairn on Shore: Maude R. Campbell, 1940 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Glympse: O.P. Mills, 1934 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - Goshen: Rosewell Page, 1940 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Gould Hill: Robert L. McElroy, 1938-1940 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Graymont: Mr. Gray, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Green Chimney Inn: F.C. McGrath, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Green Lodge: R.H. Wright, 1936-1942 (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - Green Tree: 20 acres, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 17)
      - Gum Tree Tavern: Jourdan Woolfolk, 1943 (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - Haley Dairy Farm: H.J. Haley, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 19)
      - Hanover Academy: William H. Tolenton, 1948-1955 (Box 48, Folder 20)
      - Hanover Tavern: Jourdan Woolfolk, 1938-1953 (Box 48, Folder 21)
      - Happy Hollow: Cabell Luck, 1937-1940 (Box 48, Folder 22)
      - Hill Farm: J.S. Hill, 1938-1940 (Box 48, Folder 23)
      - Holly Hill: J.R.C. Brown, 1934-1940 (Box 48, Folder 24)
      - Horse Shoe Farm: Mr. Beale, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 25)
      - Howards Mill: T.L. Stone, 1941-1944 (Box 48, Folder 26)
      - Ingleside: Joseph G. Mullen, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Ingleside: E. Turpin Philips, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Judge Grinnan Property: E.G. Cobbs, 1940 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Laurel Grove: J.M. Long, 1934-1937 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Laurel Spring: Frank P. Ebel, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Lewis Level: Jourdan Woolfolk, 1941 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Little Garden Farm: Vernell D. Vaughan, 1932-1952 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Lockwood Farm: Mrs. Clarke, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Lombardy Farm: Stephen Vaughan, 1944-1954 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Long Row: David R. Shelton, 1939-1940 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Maplewood or Hammond: 216 acres, 1930's (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Maplewood Farm: W.B. Abrams, 1953-1955 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Meadow Quarters: Stuart Wickham, 1940 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - Medley Grove: John Workman, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - Medley Grove: R.T. Carlton, 1964-1966 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - Merrie Oaks: C.H. Gordon, 1947-1950 (Box 49, Folder 16)
      - Mica Mine Farm: J.K. Poteat, 1940-1944 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - Millbrook: W.W. Amick, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - Montevideo: 1944 (Box 49, Folder 19)
      - Mount Brilliant: J.J. Rada, 1941 (Box 49, Folder 20)
      - Mount Hope: R.C. Van Sevy, 1941-1950 (Box 49, Folder 21)
      - Mount Ida: Philip Duke, 1940 (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - Mount Pleasant: Frank V. Baldwin, 1934 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Moody Place: 155 acres, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Nutshell: G. Wilson, 1944 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Nutshell: Jourdan Woolfolk, 1938-1944 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Oak Forest: L.F. Mitterer, 1939-1941 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Oak Grove: George R. Horne, 1937-1940 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Oak Grove: Nannie Hair, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Oakland Farms: A.J. Crafts, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Old Brick House Farm: R.M. Wingfield, 1936 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Pine Crest Farm: William H. Gatke, 1947-1954 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Pleasant Level: W.G. Powers, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - Pottomoi Farm: Mary L. Lafoon, 1949 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Powhite Farm: W.A. Smiley, 1936-1937 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - Prospect Hill or Pine Slash: Mary Palmer, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Puccoon: G.A. Foster, 1936-1940 (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - Quietude: Palmer, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - Rancliff Farm: A.B. Crosby, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - Range: H.G. Halle, 1940-1945 (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - Raydon: Charlotte Richeson, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - Restmore: B. Stewart Parrish, 1946-1950 (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - Retreat: E.J. Rosenburg, 1944 (Box 50, Folder 21)
      - Retreat: Reed I. West, 1959 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Rocketts: C. Lukaszkiewicz, 1935-1942 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Rocketts: Mr. Graham, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Rose Hill: William E. Langford, 1938-1952 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Salwyn: Blanche Gouldman, 1940 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Scotchtown: Annie Arnold, 1940-1956 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Shrubbery Hill Manor: Hugh Campbell, 1930 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Shrubbery Hill Manor: 1943-1951 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - Signal Hill: T.H. Dougherty, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - South Wales: Gibson Worsham, 1948 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Spring Garden Farm: Mr. Whitlock, 1940 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Spring Hill: F.B. Craxton, 1938 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Springfield Farm: J.E. Rapelye, 1940-1950 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - Stanley: Ann H. Ruffin, 1938-1939 (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - Studley Farm: Melvin Hall, 1939-1965 (Box 51, Folder 15)